Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- U.S. and International Media, 1984-2012; Series 6
  - International Labor Rights Clippings, 1984-1998; Series 6 Subseries 1
    - ILR-Honduras, 1989-1994; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - ILR-Hong Kong bulletins, 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - ILR-India "Labour Files" issues, 1996-1997; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - ILR Indonesia [1/2], 1987-1989; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - ILR-Indonesia [2/2], 1994-1996; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - ILR-Malaysia, 1988-1990; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - ILR-Mexico, 1990-1994; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - ILR-Mexico Free Trade agreement, Fast Track, 1990-1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - ILR-Middle East [1/2], 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - ILR-Middle East [2/2], 1991; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - ILR-Nicaragua [1/2], 1990; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - ILR-Nicaragua [2/2], 1994; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - ILR-Nepal, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - ILR-Panama, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - ILR-Paraguay, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - ILR-Peru, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - ILR-Phillipines, 1989-1991; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - ILR-Singapore, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - ILR-South Africa, 1984-1985; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - ILR-Taiwan, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - ILR-Thailand, 1988-1998; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - ILR-USSR, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - ILR-West Germany, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - ILR- World Trade Organization, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings and Mailings, 1985-2012; Series 6 Subseries 2
    - Local Group(s) Target Phillip-Van Heusen-Draft, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - MediaFax brochure-press releases, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Mexican Politicians Look North of Border by Robert Reinhold, New York Times, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Networking for Democracy brochure, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - New York Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Child Labor reports, 1987-1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Labor and April 25 by Bruce Occea, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Third World Resources, quarterly reviews [1/2], 1987-1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Third World Resources, quarterly reviews [2/2], 1992-1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - US Labor clippings, assorted, 1987-1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Guatemala clippings, 1988-1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - GLEP clippings [1/2], 1988-1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - GLEP Maquila [2/2], 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Colombia Solidarity booklets and flyers, 1988-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Transnationals Information Centre factsheet, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Eastern Airlines-clippings, 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters news, 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Transnational Corporations news, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Union Producers and Programmers Network (UPPNET), 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - The African American Worker-US Labor, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Coffee clippings, 1990-1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Greyhound Bus clippings, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Labor and Media, 1990-1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Labor Law news, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Women and Work-US Labor, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Guatemala Trade and Transportation clippings, 1991-1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Labor Notes, 1991-1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Labor Rights in the Jewish Tradition, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Mexico Fair Trade Campaign (1), 1991-1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - NAFTA Women's Guide (2), 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - NAFTA/General Electrics (3), 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - NAFTA analyses reports [1/2], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - NAFTA reports [2/2], 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Peacenet-NetNews, 1991-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Poultry News, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - USA-Mexico-Canada Solidarity Network, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - GSP Guatemala Newspaper Advertisement, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - GSP Press (1), 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - GSP Press (2), 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - GSP Press (3), 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - GSP Press (4), 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - GSP Press (5), 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - GSP Press (6), 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - GSP Press (7), 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Central America trade, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - CompuMentor Project, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Guatemala-assorted clippings, 1992-2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Guatemala Petition-assorted clippings, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Guatemala Petition-assorted clippings, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Oversize 163, Folder 4)
    - Guatemala Labor Press from Siglo XXI, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala Government Responds to U.S. Campaign, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - General labor press, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Levi Strauss and Company, 1992-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Nation-wide Campaign Targets Phillips-Van Heusen, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - National Day of Protests Targets U.S. Company, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - Groups Ask for Review of Guatemala's Labor Rights Situation, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - Sergio Valente-Big and Tall, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 19)
    - Southern Governor's Association conference, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 20)
    - CARE Foundation, 1993-1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 21)
    - Guatemala clippings, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 22)
    - Guatemala-coup clippings, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala GSP clippings, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Oversize 163, Folder 8)
    - Guatemala maquila news, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - The Miami Herald, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Crain's-Guatemala clippings, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Guatemala coffee, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Honduras sweatshop news, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Latin Amercia Connexiones-Casa Alianza, Guatemala, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Liz Claiborne, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Q&A Press, 1994-1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Starbucks press releases (1), 1994-1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Starbucks press (2), 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Starbucks press (3), 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Starbucks press (4), 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Starbucks press (5), 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Starbucks press (6), 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Starbucks press (7), 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Starbucks press (8), 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Starbucks clippings (9), 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Starbucks press (10), 2002-2009; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Sweatshop clipping, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Target, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Plans Expanded Trade Zone, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - World Development Movement Annual Report, 1994-1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Bob Herbert-Op-Ed, New York Times, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Burma-Macy's, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Conduct Codes-Wall Street Journal, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - "Confronting Global Power"?-Labor Research Review, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Cronica newspaper correction, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Cygne Design, Inc./Anne Taylor, 1995-1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Fox News, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Fruit of the Loom, 1995-1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - General Labor Press [1/3], 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - General Labor Press [2/3], 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - General Labor Press [3/3], 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Guatemala-H.B Fuller Company, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala-maquila drafts and clippings, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala-maquila violence, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Guatemala-Wall Street Journal correction, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - K-Mart, 1991-1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Oshkosh B'Gosh, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Newsweek Magazine-"Does Government Matter", 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 26)
    - New York Times Letter to the Editor-Guatemala sweatshops, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - New Levels of violence Against Trade Unions in Guatemala, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 28)
    - Nordstrom, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 29)
    - Starbucks Campaign coverage, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 30)
    - Why Not Productions, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 32)
    - Working Assets advertisement, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 33)
    - Brenda Starr comics, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Burlington Industries plant closings, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Clippings [1/3], 1996-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Clippings [2/3], 1998-2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Clippings [3/3], 2001-2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Colomubia Human Rights Magazine, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Guatemala Elections-"El Neuvo gabinete opina", 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Gonzalez-Press clippings, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - "Life and Death Struggle in Guatemala" by Arnie Alpert, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - National Labor Committee-Katie Lee media, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Nike, 1996-1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala Poultry, 1996-1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Kathie Lee, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - World Trade Organization, 1996; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - Banana articles, 1997-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Breakthrough for Workers Rights, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Department Stores, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - Flower campaign press, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - Jeans market, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - GSP releases, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 20)
    - Guatemala maquila press, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Oversize 163, Folder 17)
    - Hartmarx manufacturing, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - Sara Lee, 1997-1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 21)
    - Sweatshop clippings, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - T. Eaton Company, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 23)
    - The Limited, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 24)
    - "USLEAP Guide to Newsclippings"-packet, 1997-2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 31)
    - Voz Campesina (Peasant Voice), 1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 25)
    - Albertson's, inc./Jewel Food Stores, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 26)
    - Bananas-Dole, Philippines, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 27)
    - Banana Link news, 1998-1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 28)
    - Chiquita Press Releases, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 29)
    - Council of Hemispheric Affairs-Chiquita press releases, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 144, Folder 30)
    - Dillard's, Inc., 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Fair Trade press clippings, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala newspaper clipping, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala newspaper clipping originals-bananas, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Hurricane Mitch clippings, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - International Union Rights Vol.5, Issue 2, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - McCormick and Company, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Nestle, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - NUK research-online sources, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - World Trade Organization-Bananas, 1998-1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Bananas-Washington Post article, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Del Monte articles, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Del Monte press, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Dole Layoffs-clippings, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - "Making Kathie Lee Cry"-Wall Street Journal, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - "Taming the Tiger in Honduras" by Kirk S. Bowman, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - "Anti-Sweatshop Movement" by Steven Greenhouse, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - Del Monte agreement [1/2], 2000; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Del Monte agreement [2/2], 2000; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - Dole-Chile clippings, 2000; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - Nike press, 2000-2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - Regis Philbin Sweatshop scandal, 2000; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 32)
    - Colombia press, 2001-2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - Dole-Euroban press release, 2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 23)
    - "Floral Derangement" Harper's Magazine article, 2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 24)
    - Guatemala clippings, 2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Oversize 163, Folder 21)
    - New York Times clippings, 2001-2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 25)
    - Unions-New York Times, 2001; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 26)
    - Bananas-Los Alamos press, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 27)
    - Banana Press-Noboa-New York Times, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 28)
    - Coca-Cola, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 29)
    - "Coffee-bean oversupply deepens Latin America's Woes" by Peter Fritsch, Wall Street Journal, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 30)
    - Ecuador forced to redress banana worker rights, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 31)
    - Ecuador clippings, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 32)
    - Ecuador newspapers, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 33)
    - Liz Clairborne-Aida Carolina, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 34)
    - Noboa press, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 35)
    - Venezuela labor, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 36)
    - Victoryt at Alcoa; Labor Alerts, 2002; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 37)
    - Flower press, 2003-2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 38)
    - Tarrant articles, 2003-2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - El Salvador-Gap, Inc./UNITE, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - "Lost Jobs a bitter brew" by Sabrina Eaton, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Mexico's Deplorable Runaway Maquiladoras: Another Example: "Flor de Baja" by Gema Lpez Limn, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - "Mexican Workers Sweat on labour ruling" -Financial Times, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - ORIT info-International Workers Day, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Pepsi Boycott, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - "Roddick Tarets 'sweatshop' shame", 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Sweat X closes, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - "Victory for Haitian Workers in Free Trade Zone!", 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - "Wal-Mart's expansion is not necesarily a boon for Mexico", 2004; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Florecer newspaper, 2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Maquila media coverage, 2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Mexico/Barbie-New York Times, 2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Mexico-Rubie's/Mattel, 2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Tarrant Apparel Group and Federated Department Stores Amend Exclusive Distribution Agreement for American Rag CIE, 2005; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Colombia-Dole flowers, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Colombia-Dole flowers, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Colombia press clippings and coverage summary, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Colombia Union press, 2006-2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Colombia violence-Washington Post, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - The Packer articles-Dole and Chiquita, 2006-2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - USA Today, 2006-2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - El Salvador-Just Garments closing, LA Times, 2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 23)
    - Florecer, 2007-2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 24)
    - "Getting to a Colombia Trade Deal" -New York Times, 2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Labor Rights and Law coverage-Colombia and Guatemala, 2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 26)
    - Colombia-New York Times Op=Ed rebuttal, 2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - Labor rights and law coverage-Colombia and Guatemala, 2007; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 25)
    - Colombia-New York Times Op-Ed rebuttal, 2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 27)
    - COLSIBA-bananas, 2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 28)
    - Colombia Trade Pact, 2008; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 29)
    - Colombia Aid/Obama administration, 2009; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 30)
    - Colombia labor-newspapers, 2009; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Alien Tort Statute ruling, 2010; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 32)
    - Haitian Apparel Industry, post-earthquake, 2010; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 33)
    - Excellon Resources, Incorporated, 2011-2012; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 34)
    - David Bacon articles-Labor Law, 2011; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 35)
    - Colombia banana news, 2011; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 36)
    - Colombia Solidarity Center critique, 2012; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 37)
  - USLEAP Press Releases, 1991-2010; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Press Statement, SITRABI/Del Monte, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - GLEP-Led Delegation Finds Massive Labor Rights Abuses in Guatemala, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Labor, Human Rights Petitioners Target Guatemala Rights Abuses, 1991; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - U.S. groups Call Guatemala n Government Response on Worker Rights Insufficient to Retain Trade Benefits, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Congressional Members Call for Investigation of Workers Rights Abuses in Guatemala, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - U.S. to Investigate Labor Rights Abuses in Guatemala, 1992; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Guatemala's Trade Benefits Remain in Question, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - National Day of Protests Held Against U.S. Companies, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Potential Break-through in Guatemala's Maquiladora Sector, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Shareholders Call on U.S. Company to Respect Basic Rights of Workers in Guatemala, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - US Group Seeks Extension of Guatemala Trade Benefits, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - US Government Refuses to End Workers Rights Investigation, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Petitioners on Guatemala Workler Rights Agree to Six-Month Extension of Trade Benefits, 1993; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Guatemala GSP-Trade Probation, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Guatemala Sugar Exports, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - GSP-US Extends Trade Probation, 1994; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Starbucks Releases Code of Conduct for Coffee, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Extends Guatemala's Trade Probation, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Phillips-Van Heusen Agrees to Negotiate, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala Trade/Del Monte, 1998; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Campaign against Fresh Del Monte, 1999; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Tarrant Releases, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Trade Petitions against Ecuador, 2004; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Colombian Flower Workers, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Dole/Human Rights press release, 2006; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Summary Press Coverage: Release of AFL-CIO Report "Justice for All", 2006; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - Colombia Justice System/Murder of Trade Unionists, 2010; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 147, Folder 28)
- Stephen Coats Papers, 1984-2012; Series 7